I do not know   feels like a grave.
我不知道  感觉像是坟墓
Their queen is here.
他们的王后在这里
And we have our orders.
我们按命令行事
It's a trap.
这是个陷阱
This is what is known.
这些是众所皆知的
There has always been man.
自有人类以来
And there have always been vampires.
就有吸血鬼
Since the beginning   the two have been locked in conflict.
二个种族自从开始就一直冲突不断
The vampire was the hunter and stronger.
吸血鬼速度快 也比较强壮
But the man had the sun.
不过人类有太阳
It was not enough.
但是 这样是不够的
And so it went like this over many years.
就这样过了很多年
The two races destroying not only each other
两个种族不止是互相毁灭
but the world itself.
也毁灭地球
Faced against extinction   mankind has
人类再度面临灭绝
retreated behind the walls of cities
只能退缩到城市的墙后
under the protection of the Church.
躲在教会的保护之下
And then the ultimate weapon was found   the priests.
而后人类找到终极武器  猎魔教士
Warriors with the extraordinary powers
他们是有不凡力量的战士
trained by the Church at the art of vampire combat.
由教会传授吸血鬼的战斗技巧
They alone turned the tide to man.
他们为人类获得胜利
The remaining vampires were placed in reservations.
剩下的吸血鬼被保留下来
And fearing of the power of the weapon they created
他们害怕猎魔教士的力量
the ruling clerics ordered the priests to disband.
神职人员解散了猎魔教士
Former warriors integrated into a society
猎魔教士进入了一个
that no longer needed them.
不再需要他们的社会
And as the years passed   the few surviving preasts
又过了许多年  剩下的猎魔教士
faded into obscurity
渐渐被遗忘
like the vampire mass before them.
就如同他们之前的吸血鬼
Priest.
片名《猎魔教士》
Residual readiation is still spotted.
还是有辐射残留
The contamination is close to zero.
污染快消散了
With a little luck   we can finally start planting.
运气好一点  我们可以开始种些东西
I am proud of you   Owen.
我以你为荣  欧文
Great   we'll eat stewed leaks.
太好了 我们可以吃炖的东西了
- Atoning for your sins?  - No   why?
- 你刚是去告解吗?  - 不是 怎了?
Wearing the nicest dress   where else would you be except the church?
穿这样不是去教会还会去哪
I was in town.
我进城了
I think that at least someone should have a life outside this place.
总得有人在这个地方之外有个不同的生活
I said I didn't want you to spend so much time out there.
我说过我不要你花太多时间在外面
I'm old enough to go where I want.
我大到可以决定我想去那
18 is not old enough   out here.
18岁在外面还不够
I know it's hard but we all have to make sacrifices.
我知道这不容易  我们都得要牺牲一点
Sacrifices ?!
牺牲?
Living here like a prisoner ?! Without friends   no fun ?!
活在这像个犯人一样? 没有任何朋友 乐趣?
Just that someday you could grow something
只希望有天你能在这片荒芜的土地上
in these godforsaken lands?
种点什么东西出来?
Enough!
够了
Hold hands and say grace.
握着手   说感谢上帝
Dear Lord   thank you for the food we are about to recieve
亲爱的上帝  感谢你赐给我们食物
-Daddy?  -Huh
- 爸爸  - 嘘!
- Owen? - Tear down below!  - What's going on ?!
- 欧文?  - 打开下面  - 怎么回事?
Hurry child!
快点  孩子
Hurry!
快点
Whatever you hear   don't scream.
不管听到什么 别尖叫
Stand behind me!
站在我后面
Shannon!
夏侬!
CHURCH CITY: SECTOR 12
教会城市  12区
God protects you   the Church protects you.
上帝保护你  教会保护你
The city protects you.
城市保护你
Absolution of sin   is the only way.
赦免是唯一的路
Remember   be against the Church   means to go against God.
记住 反抗教会就是反抗上帝
Cabin no confession. 5   is free.
告解室五号  可以使用
Move forward.
向前移动
Initiate confessional sequence.
启动告解系统
To use   say   speak at the time.
若要使用  请同时开始说话
Forgive me Father   for I have sinned.
请赦免我 神父
- Yes   my son? - I had the dream again.
- 是的 我的孩子? - 我又再次梦到那场战争
On War. Tell me more.
继续说
We were in the hives   like always.
我们在巢里  一如以往
Eastbound   and I wasn't strong enough.
向东  我不够强壮
Tell me more.
继续说
I have questions   doubts.
我有问题 疑虑
The Devil comes in many shapes.
恶魔以各种面貌现身
The best way to combat him   through personel sacrifice
要克服他们最好的方式就是个人牺牲
and labor.
和努力不懈
Yes Father.
是的 神父
Now say three Hail Mary's and four Our Father's.
现在各赞美圣母玛丽亚三次和上帝四次
And remember   to go against the Church   means to go against God.
记住 反抗教会就是反抗上帝
Stop pointing fingers.
别乱指人 这样很不礼貌
To tatoo.
他脸上有刺青
Did it hurt?
会痛吗
- Why can't I talk?  - You can't talk to priests.
- 为什么我不能说话?  - 你不能和教士说话
- Who are you?  - Name's Hicks   on the Sheriff from Augustine.
- 你是谁?  - 我是希克斯 从奥古斯丁来的警长
What do you want?
你来干啥的?
There was a vamp attack.
吸血鬼发动攻击  他们带走了露西
to Lucy. Your brother is hurt bad. He told me where to find you.
你兄弟伤的很重 他告诉我在哪可以找到你
And Shannon?
那夏侬呢?
Lucy talked about you. Said you were here during the war.
露西谈过你 说你是战时的英雄
Said when killing vampires you were the best.
杀吸血鬼你最行
I'm going after her   I'm gonna get her back.
我要去找她  把她找回来
Just thought that to let you know in case you wanted to come along.
只是想让你知道  你也许想和我一起去
Figure out I could use
like you by my side.
OK.
好吧
Thank you for meeting me in such short notice Monsignors.
谢谢你在这么短的时间内见我  主教
Monsignor Chamberlain has informed us of the situation.
张伯伦主教告诉了我们情形
- Your family is in our prayers.  - Thank you.
- 我们为你的异变者祷告  - 谢谢
I come before you because I want my authority reinsated.
我到这是希望能恢复我的职权
On what grounds?
有什么理由呢
- This was a vampire attack.  - Vampires?
- 这是次吸血鬼攻击  - 吸血鬼?
Nonsense   we've had no reports
胡说  我们没收到报告
of any escapes from the reservations.
有关于吸血鬼从保留区逃走
This is obviously the work of bandits.
这显然是反抗军干的
- Monsignor   boy was clear.  - "The boy" was mistaken.
- 这孩子说的很清楚了  - 他搞错了
There is no vampire manace   the wastelands are haevens for lawless and
没有吸血鬼攻击  荒地是不法之徒的天堂
as a priest you would not except a thing like this ridiculous and futile.
身为教士  你不该信这些荒谬又无聊的东西
It is best left to local authorities.
最好是由当地的执法者来处理
Monsignor Orelas   this man has been a great service to the Church.
Orelas主教  这个人曾对教会有过极大的贡献
Were it not for the priest we would have been overrun
如果没有他  我们不可能战胜
We are all aware of his accomplishments Monsignor Chamberlain.
我们都了解他的成就 张伯伦主教
Thank you   can you sit down.
谢谢 请你坐下
I'm begging you.
我请求你
- Allow me to find them.  - You have to understand something priest.
- 让我去找他们  - 你要了解一件事  教士
Sanctity of these walls is absolute.
在墙后绝对是圣洁的
The citizens from the cities have complete faith in
市民对教会的能力有十足的信心
the Church's ability to keep them safe.
认为我们能保证他们的安全
You will not shake that faith.
你不能动摇这份信心
How can that faith be when it's a lie?
当信念变谎言还有意义吗?
Questioning the authority of the clergy is absolutelt forbidden.
质疑当局是绝对不允许的
If you take any action to leave the cities
如果你采取任何行动离开城市
it will be seem as an act of agression against the Church.
就会被视为是反抗教会的行为
You will be stripped from the order and excommunicated. Did I make myself clear?
你会被逐出教会  我说得够清楚了吧
I said   do I make myself clear father?
我说得够清楚了吧  教士
Yes Monsignor.
是的 主教
Try to remember your vow. To go against Church is to go against God.
记住你的誓言  反抗教会就是反抗上帝
Come on now. Don't be shy.
来  别害羞
Give us a kiss.
给我们一个吻
That's no way to treat a friend.
这不是待客之道
Please   let me go
请让我走
You are here for your own protection.
你在里面这是为了保护你自己
If you go out you shall be taken apart   piece by piece.
如果你出去是会被撕成一片片的
My uncle is a priest   he'll come after me.
我叔叔是教士  他会来救我的
Really?
真的吗?
- What makes you so sure?  - He'll come after me.
- 你怎这么肯定?  - 他会来救我的
He'll come after you!
他会来干掉你!
Well that's something I'm absolutely counting on.
我坚信他一定不会来
The judgement is final. I'm sorry.
抱歉  判决已经定案了
I sacrificed everything that's worldly.
牺牲一切是值得的
- And they won't listen to me.  - The war is long gone.
- 他们就是不听我的话  - 战争早已结束
You and the other priests have done their jobs.
你和其它的教士已完成使命
It's not over   not for me.
对我而言  还没结束
You can't break your covenant on a small
你不能破坏你的誓约
group of savages would be sacrilige.
只因为一小群的吸血鬼
I have to.
我得这样做
That's what I was afraid of.
这是我最怕发生的事
If you go out now   you risk sturring things up again.
如果你现在出去  就得再次冒险
You have to look at the bigger picture   it's for the greater good.
你得顾全大局
- Is it the same world that I fought for?  - No.
- 这还是当初我奋斗换来的世界吗  - 不是
But it's the only one we have left.
但这是我们仅有的
I'm begging you   don't do anything foolish.
我求你  你别再做傻事了
Remember your vow   to go against the Church is to go against God.
记住你的誓言  反抗教会就是反抗上帝
Then I go against God.
那我就反抗上帝
God help us.
上帝救救我们
Dear Father   forgive me.
亲爱的上帝  请原谅我
It was never my intention to offend you.
我不是故意要冒犯你
I'd like to firmly resolve with the help of your grace
我想要在你的恩赐下解决
no more mistakes   and avoid the occasions of sin.
不再犯错  不再犯罪
But I can't.
但我不能
Looting is not such a good idea mister.
抢劫不是个好主意
Well I'll be damned.
我会被诅咒
Vampires are a vicious lie!
吸血鬼是不实的谎言
I saw a vampire bite off a man in half.
我看过吸血鬼把人咬成二段
Salvation is right here   in my very hands.
救赎就在这  在我的手里
- Authenticated of the clergy themself    - Wait me for a moment.
- 教士证实过的  - 等我一下
And keep more loved ones safe one more night
保护你所爱的人再度过安全的一晚
I'm tired of you comin' around here   scaring people with more superstition.
我不想再看到你在这用迷信吓人
The show is over   it's time for you to go.
散会了  你该走了
Give me one good reason why I should.
有什么理由我该走
It's one   two
这是一个   二个
OK   OK   OK !!
好好好
Goddamn son of a bitch!
真他妈的混球
All listen up!
听好了!
The stuff is good for nothin'
这些都只不过是那个人
but lies for that man's pockets for your hard earned cash!
要骗你们辛勤工作赚来的钱
You don't know that. You're just a kid.
你根本就不知道 你不过是个孩子.
We gotta do somethin' to keep us safe.
我们要做点事来保持我们的安全
Move out of the way !!
别挡路
I don't anyone for being scared.
我不想任何人感到害怕
The vampires are gone and they're not coming back.
吸血鬼走了  不会再回来
You have to excuse the attention. Strangers are not here often.
不要惹人注意  陌生人不常在这出现
Is it true what they say about priests?
他们说的有关教士的传闻是真的吗?
To be the hand of God?
上帝的左右手?
How is he?
他怎样了?
He's in rest.
他醒了
Claire took the boys
教会把你带走时 还不过是个小孩
A return of an old man.
回来时你已经是个大人了
After the war was over
战争结束后
Shannon figured you'll come back.
夏侬说过你会回来
I wanted to.
我想回来
But I can't see right and wrong.
但我分不清什么是对是错
I couldn't save her.
我救不了她
I tried   but I've never had your gift.
我试过了  但我没有你的天赋
You gave her a life that I have more I could not.
你给了她我不能给她的生活
He'll always be greatful for her.
我会一直感激你
You know there ain't one day she didn't forget about you.
你知道她总有一天会忘了你
You'll find Lucy   and bring her home safe.
你要找到露西  把她安全带回家
And you promise me something brother.
答应我  兄弟
Kill 'em all.
把他们全干掉
Most people out there know that the clergy thinks of us as Godless people.
大部份的人知道教士认为我们是无神论者
And that's how we like it. It means that they'll keep their noses out of our business.
我们喜欢这样  这表示他们不会来管我们
As you can imagine how surprised I was when they concacted me asking if I'd seen you.
你可以想像我有多惊讶他们叫我来找你
Saying that anyone going after Lucy is to be arrested immediately.
说任何去找露西的人都会被逮捕
Said she's in God's hands now.
说她在上帝的手中了
Problem is
问题是
we both now outside this place she'd be dead
我们俩都知道出了这地方她就死定了
or worse   infected.
更糟的是可能被感染了
With all due respect to God
看在上帝的份上
You're wasting your time.
你是在浪费时间
You're not cutting me out of this! I'm the one that came and got you!
你别把我排除在外 是我去找你的
The people in this town don't think you can keep them safe here.
镇上的人不认为你能保证他们的安全
What makes you think you'll do any good out there?
你凭什么认为你能做神马好事?
- You ant good with a gun?  - Better than I am with a knife.
- 你枪法如何?  - 比我用刀还好
We leave at dawn.
我们清晨离开
What's with all these bullets anyway?
这些子弹是做什么用的?
I thought that priests did not use firearms.
我还以为教士是不用枪的
We don't.
我们不用
These are for you.
这些是给你的
You are called to serve once more.
你们再度被召唤
One of your own has broken his sacred vow.
现在你们之中 已有人打破誓言
His actions are a threat to the entire order.
他的行为是个威胁
You'll find him and bring him back to me.
你们要找到他并把他带回来
Dead or alive.
活要见人 死要见尸
- What is it?  - Vampire tracks are round and
- 这是什么?  - 吸血鬼足迹是圆的
in sets of 2   3 or 4 at once   these are two by two.
通常一次有2~4个 而这些是2个2个的
Must have been some of the familiars.
一定是他们的异变者
Vampires don't bring familiars. In the hunt they slow them down.
吸血鬼不会带异变者  只会让他们慢下来
All this
这些是
This was something else.
这些是别的东西
Tracks head north.
足迹朝北走
- There's a reservation that way.  - Well then   that's where we start.
- 有个保留区在那里  - 那我们就从那里开始
Mangshane Reservation. Talk about the red out in jacks.
曼沙保留区 谈谈红色插孔里面的(???)
They're a fallen tribe.
他们是个没落家族
Either way   we don't have much time to get in and out.
不管如何  我们都没有太多时间进出
No guards.
没有警卫
I thought familiars were illegal.
我以为家族是不合法的
No one ever enforces it   as long as it's voluntary.
没人强制  只要他是自愿
- Voluntary?  - Yes   come to the border.
- 自愿?  - 是啊在边界就是这样
Drifters that want to get infected.
游民想要被感染
They think becoming a vampire and live among them.
他们想成为吸血鬼生活
They have all sorts of strange ideas. As long as they keep to themselves I
他们有奇怪的想法  只要他们安份
Makes no difference to me.
对我是没差
You're not welcome priest.
这里不欢迎你  教士
These lands are protected.
这土地受到保护
I got this.
我了解
We're looking for a local girl   kidnapped 4 nights ago by vampires.
我们在找一个四天前被吸血鬼绑架的女孩
- They came through this neighborhood.  - Nobody comes through Nightshade.
- 他们从这经过  - 没人会从曼沙保留区经过
So it's nice
所以这里又漂亮
and quiet.
又安静
Good   we're sure we don't have any trouble.
很好 我相信我们不会碰到麻烦
They excreet it   use them to build the hives.
他们排泄出来的  用来建巢
I guess we now what happened to the guards.
我想我们知道这些警卫是发生什么事了
No   no   no   you must not
不不不  你不行
The Master will be angry
主人会生气
Where's the girl?
女孩在哪?
I don't know what you're talking about.
我不知道你在说什么
The Master doesn't feed anymore.
主人不再喂我们了
Tell that to the guards.
跟警卫说去
- Where is she?  - Please don't   don't
- 她在哪?  - 拜托 不要  不要
Where is she?
她在哪?
Priest !! Priest !!!
教士! 教士!
Save your bullets.
省省你的子弹
We can do this the easy way or
我们可以轻松一点还是
God. I always prefered the hard way.
我还是喜欢痛苦一点的
Tell me where you took the girl.
告诉我你把那女孩带到哪去了
Haven't you done already priest ?!
你做的还不够吗 教士?
- Tell me!  - Look around   what we've done to them.
- 告诉我  - 你看看  他们对我们做了什么
They once ruled this land   they were  worriers   they were Gods.
他们曾经统治这片土地 他们是战士也是神
- They were murderers.  - They were what they were made to be.
- 他们是杀人魔  - 这是他们的天性
-   in nature just like you.  - You have 10 seconds to start talking.
- 就像你一样  - 你有十秒可以讲话
10 seconds is all I need. You're too late priest.
也只剩十秒了 你大难临头了 教士
This is their time now.
现在是他们的时间了
- Did you get your gun on?  - Why?
- 你有带枪吗?  - 做什么?
You're gonna need it.
你会用到的
I walk to the shadow of death
我走过死亡的阴影
-   fear no evil.  - Your words mean nothing to them priest.
- 不怕邪恶  - 你的言语对他们是没用的 教士
For Thou are with me.
因上帝和我同在
Focus!
专心!
Should we go after them?
我们该去追他们吗
No need   they'll die at first light.
没必要  一旦日出他们就死了
No more masters   just you and me.
没有主人了  只有你和我
Tell me where they took the girl.
告诉我  他们把女孩带去哪了
- West   they took her west.  - Why?
- 西边  他们带她去西边了  - 为什么?
You have no idea what's coming priest.
你不知你要面对的是什么 教士
The familiar said they travel west from here.
异变者说他们由此向西
- Solar wall.  - A hive?
- 太阳墙  - 一个巢穴?
One of the largest.
最大的一个
But I thought all the hives were destroyed at the war.
我还以为这些巢穴在战争时都被毁了
They were.
曾经是
That's why we need to go look.
这就是为什么我们要去看看
There are more than 50 crips in this reservation.
曾有超过50个吸血鬼在这保留区
But only 6 vampires left. The weak.
但只有6个弱的被留下
They left behind. We find the missing one   we find Lucy.
我们找到其他的 就能找到露西
I may not have seen the war
我也许没看过战争
but I know the look a man gets when he likes killing.
但我还是看得出一个人是不是喜欢杀人
It comes easy to you.
对你是很容易
I just can't.
我就是不行
Lucy's got nothing to do with it.
容不容易没有关系
Give me your gun.
把你的枪给我
- What?  - Give me your gun.
- 什么?  - 把你的枪给我
Vampires are not like humans.
吸血鬼不像人一样
Their body weight pulls them in concentrated patterns.
他们的体重使他们处在集中模式
You need to anticipate their trajectory to make a kill shot.
你要预测他们的行径才能杀了他们
Are you teaching me to shoot?
你是在教我如何开枪?
I'm teaching you how to kill vampires.
我是在教你如何杀吸血鬼
There are always 2 points. A and B.
有二个要点 A和B
Know 'em both   you'll kill a vampire.
了解这二个要点 你就能杀吸血鬼
A man came aboard. Says he got something for you.
有个人来  说他有东西要给你
You told me to come.
你要我来
I have information   but I
我有讯息  但我
Before I tell you   I hate to bring you this.
在我告诉你前  我要先拿这个
There is this small little matter of compensation.
要有点小小的酬劳
You want   it'll be real good for business.
你一直是个好伙伴
So I'm more willing to cut you a deal.
所以我很乐意让你杀价
Can you smell the blood running through you veins?
你能闻到在你血管中的血吗?
Smells like dinner.
闻起来像是晚餐
OK. Allright.
好了 好了
Once you have grabbed that girl   a couple of nights later   a priest showed up.
你抓了那女孩后 过了几晚 那教士就出现
- Priest?  - And he was with this Sheriff.
- 教士?  - 他和警长在一起
Real hard case   he run me out of town before I could make a single sell.
真是麻烦的案子  我没卖一个就被赶出来了
- You've done well.  - Thank you.
- 你做的很好  - 谢谢
There's you compensation.
这是你的酬劳
Put him to work.
带他去工作
I came here when I was little.
我小时候来过这
Stared all his stuff.
看着这些
He wondered what it used to be.
想像以前是怎样
After a while   it just makes my eyes ache.
过了一阵子  这只令我眼睛痛
Did Owen know about you and Lucy?
欧文知道你和露西的事吗?
No   no.
不 不
She wanted to tell him   but
她想告诉他但是
Owen wasn't the easiest man to talk to.
欧文不是个好说话的人
Besides   he was so focused on his work that he didn't care of things.
另外 他只专注于工作上 不管其它的事
Do you love her?
你爱她吗
If she's infected
如果她被感染了
I'll kill her.
我会杀了她
You'll try
你可以试试
but you won't be able to.
你不会成功的
I wasn't there to protect her once   I won't make the same mistake again.
我曾不能保护她 我不会犯第二次错
- Feels like a grave.  - It's a trap.
- 像是坟墓一样  - 这是个陷阱
This is a waste of time  there's nothing there.
这是在浪费时间 这里什么也没有
Stay here   if anything comes up that isn't me   shoot it.
待在这  如果有什么东西出现 不是我 就开枪
Great.
太好了
- What are you doing here? - The Clergy sent me. Ordered me to bring you back.
- 你在这做什么? - 他们要我来带你回去
They sent four of us to track you. We split up at Nightshade.
他们派了四个人来找你 我们在NightShade分开
I really hoped they didn't have you.
我真希望他们没找到你
The others went up to Jericho.
其他人去了Jericho
I didn't believe when they told me you broke your vow.
我不相信他们说你打破了誓言
They left me no choice. Hicks!
希克斯  我别无选择
What the hell was that thing ?!
那是什么鬼东西?
- A guard.  - Who the hell are you ?!
- 一个警卫  - 你又是谁?!
It's too big to get down here.
这里大到找不到路下来
Which is the only reason you're still alive.
这就是你还活着的原因
Who the hell is that?
那是什么鬼东西
Are you ready?
准备好了吗
Not bad.
不错麻
Point A   meet point fucking B.
点A  到点B
The hive's been abandoned for years. Why would it need anyone protect it?
这个巢已经废弃好多年了  为何要保护它?
Does he know what you'll do if she's infected?
他知道如果她被感染了你会做什么吗?
He knows.
他明白
- He will try to stop you.  - He won't be able to.
- 他会阻止你  - 他没那能力
It's been hard for all these years.
这些年很辛苦
Can't see the others   no talking.
不能见其它人  不能说话
Sector 7 was the only place I could find work.
7区是我唯一可以找到工作的地方
Waste management.
废物管理
No one would hire "A girl who kills".
没人要雇用一个"会杀人的女孩"
I heard that.
我听说了
I didn't come here to bring you back.
我不是要来带你回去
I came here to warn you.
我是来警告你的
There are nights. When I wake up
有时晚上  当我醒来
I think I'm back on the red mines.
我以为我回到红矿
I'm sweating   I clench   like I'm ready for something.
我流汗 咬牙 像是我准备要做什么一样
At those nights I go back to sleep.
在那些晚上我回去睡觉时
I have bad dreams.
我做了恶梦
Me too.
我也是
The other nights   the good nights
其它的晚上 美好的晚上
I dream about other things.
我梦到其它事
- Why doesn't it look like the rest of the hive?  - This section here   they must have realtered.
- 为什么看来不像其它的巢?  - 这里有重建过
Oh my God.
我的天
They bread a new army.
他们在建立新的军队
Where did they all go?
他们都去哪了?
Only one way out.
只有一个出口
Are priests allowed relations?
教士可以结婚吗?
- We take a vow of celibacy.  - You mean   you never
- 我们的誓言不能打破  - 你是说 你从没 ..
I was a young girl when the Clergy found me.
当我还是个小女孩时 教会找上我
What about him?
那他呢
You can follow in my footsteps  or you can follow in his.
你可以跟着我的脚步  或是跟他的
He was you age when the Clergy came for him.
他们找上他时和你一样大
Therefore   his sacrifice is bigger than most.
然而 他的牺牲也是最大的
The air is changing.
空气不一样了
Well there's you answer.
这是你要的答案
They dug right through the mountain and
他们挖穿了山
Made a hole big enough to fit a whole army through.
大到可以让军队过去
What town is that?
那是什么镇?
It's Jericho.
是Jericho
Where'd you say the others went?
你刚说其它人往那去了?
What the hell?
搞什么?
Hello ?!
Hello!
Is anybody there?
有人吗?
Let's begin.
我们开始吧
I don't see anything.
我看不到任何东西
Brothers. You have a choice.
兄弟 你有个选择
You can follow in my footsteps  or you can follow in his.
你可以跟着我的脚步  或是跟他的
We're too late.
我们太迟了
We seperate   go for each building  and see what we can find.
我们分开 去每栋建筑物里 看看能找到什么
There's nobody left   no soul.
什么人也没找到
Too many mouths to feed.
太多嘴巴要喂了
Killing three priests? What kind of vampire can do something like that?
杀了三个教士?什么样的吸血鬼有这般能耐
Nothing we've ever seen before.
我们从没见过的
How could they clean an entire town over night   and vanish by sunrise?
他们如何能清光整个镇并在日出之前离开?
There are no hives around here   no reservations.
这附近没巢  也没保留区
- Where does this rail line go?  - It's an old mining line.
- 这轨道是去哪?  - 去一个旧矿区
It starts at Dunker  passing through Augustine.
从Dunker开始经由奥古斯丁
- Jericho is the last stop before    - The cities.
Jerico是到城市前的终点站   -城里
If they reach cities it would be suicide   right?
他们到城市的话就是自杀 对吧?
- The sun will kill them.  - There is no sun in the cities.
- 太阳会杀了他们.  - 在城市没有太阳
Not anymore.
不会有了
Without us   they're defensless.
没我们  他们毫无招架之力
- I'm responsible.  - No   this was sistematic.
- 是我的错  - 不 这是有计昼的
Whoevet took Lucy   knew you'd come for her
带走露西的人  知道你会来找她
and we'd come for you.They're drawing us out.
然后我们会来找你  他们引我们出来
They must have picked up different factions during the day   and through the night.
他们一定是分批走
- It's going to be a massacre.  - It's going to be a war.
- 这会是场大屠杀  - 这会是一场战争
Train carrying an army of vampires?
火车带有一群吸血鬼大军?
What chance do we have stopping something like that?
我们有什么机会能阻止他们?
I'll take the train and blow the line.You two get aboard and find Lucy.
我去火车那炸了他们  你们两个去找露西
I'll start charging the bikes.
我会把车子充好电.
It's gonna take everything we have
我们要带上所有的东西
to stop the train before it reaches the cities.
来阻止火车到达城市
You must be starving.You haven't eaten in days.
你一定是饿了  你好几天没吃东西了
Have you ever had a real roast duck?
你吃过真的烤鸭吗?
It's very rare   real exotic.
很少会有的
- Of course not.  - Try it   you'll never have better.
- 当然没有  - 吃看看 你不会再吃到好东西了
- What do you want?  - I want the same things that you want.
- 你要什么?  - 我要的跟你要的是一样的
I want to be free from a life of suffering and sacrifice.
我要没有痛苦和牺牲的生活
To no longer be told to your every desire as a sin.
你的欲望不再是罪恶
And after all   if you're not commiting sin   you're nor having fun.
毕竟 要是你不犯罪就没乐子了
What are you?
你是什么?
The Church teaches us that the eyes are the window to the soul
教会说眼睛是灵魂之窗
and since the vampire are evolved without eyes   it is a soulles creature
吸血鬼演化到没有眼睛  因此他们没有灵魂
that should be eradicated.
所以该杀
And I have seen the soul of the vampire.And let me tell you
我感受到吸血鬼的灵魂.让我来告诉你
it's far more pure than any man.
他比任何人的灵魂更纯洁
Now you ask me what I am.
现在你问我 我是什么
I am the bringer of the tide
我是这个时代的代表
I am the way for the wash clean this unclean world.
我要彻底清洗这个不洁的世界
And you and your priest
而你和你的教士
will help me do it.
会帮我完成它
He's gonna kill her.Isn't it...if she's infected?
如果她感染了...他是不是会杀了她?
She talked about him.Said she never known him.
她谈过他 说她从不了解他
She wanted to.
她想要
What kind of man would kill his own flesh and blood?
什么样的人会杀了他的亲骨肉?
If she becomes a follower  she's no ones flesh and blood.
如果她成为他们的一员  她就不是谁的骨肉
Not anymore.
再也不是
Held on to it   all there years.
这些年来 一直坚持着
To remind me what they've stripped away from us.
提醒我他们从我们这拿走什么
our honor,our abilities,our faith
我们的荣誉  我们的能力  我们的信仰
Today I want you to remember
今天我要你记着
that our power doesn't come from the Church
我们的能力不是来自教会
it comes from God.
而是来自上帝
With or without clergy  we're still priests.
不论有没有教会  我们都还是教士
I can't.
我不能
When I heard what happened to Shannon
当我听到夏侬的事
I prayed for her salvation.
我为她的救赎祈祷
And then I prayed for mine.
也为我自己祈祷
Because of the darkness in my heart.
因为在我的心里有阴影
I hoped her death would free you at last.
我希望她的死会让你最终得到解放
- Tell me you won't kill her.  - Hicks,don't do this.
- 告诉我你不会杀她  - 希克斯 别这样
Tell me,or I'll shoot you in your place.
告诉我,不然我会杀了你
It's easier to face you bullet here than face the thing what's up ahead.
你杀了我比去面对他们简单多了
Why do you even care? She's nothing but a stranger to you.
你在意吗? 她对于你只不过是个陌生人
She's his daughter.
她是他的女儿
She was just a baby when the clergy took me.
当我被教会带走时 她只是个小女孩
You're lying   I knew Owen.
你说谎 我了解欧文
The child needed a father.
她需要一个父亲
We all made sacrifices.
我们都做了牺牲
Hicks.
希克斯
If you do this,you will wonder if you find Lucy..
如果你这么做 你将会质疑自己是否能救出Lucy...
You won't stop the train, and you won't be able to save them.
你阻止不了火车,你也救不了他们
You want me safer.
你还是希望我安全点吧
We will get this made together.
让我们一起完成它
When the train comes, you blow the tracks and get out of there !!
火车来就炸了 快走
What if you're still on the train ?!
你为何还在车上?
Good luck.
祝你好运
Focus!
专心
Holy shit.
天啊
Hello my friend.
你好 我的朋友
- You fell!  - You let go!
- 你掉下去了  - 你放手了
In the depths of that hive   I touched the threshold of life and death.
当时在那巢中 我越过生死边缘
And do you know what I found?
你知道我找到了什么吗?
The queen might come to kill  but she gave me mercy.
王后可以杀了我  但是她怜悯我
She turned me into something that never existed in this world.
她把我变成这世上从没有过的东西
A human vampire.
一个人类吸血鬼
Join me   accept the blood of the queen.
加入我 接受王后的血
Together we can return to the cities
我们一起回到城市
as brothers.
如同兄弟一样
- Where is my daughter?  - Waiting for your decision.
- 我的女儿在哪?  - 等你的决定
You can't win.I'm stronger now than you ever were.
你赢不了 我现在比你强太多了
This is your last chance Priest.
这是你最后的机会 教士
The queens's hands can not be denied.
女王的好意不能拒绝
Mankind will find no hideout of what's coming.
人类是逃不了的
Join me   and your life of sacrifice will be over.
加入我 你的牺牲生活就结束了
Never.
绝不
Hicks!
希克斯!
Lucy!
露西!
- Fuck.  - Did you find her?
- 该死  - 你找到她了?
I couldn't get closer.They took her to the front.
我接近不了她 他们带她到前面去了
- You would have made a good priest.  - Thanks.
- 你会成为一个好教士  - 谢谢
Don't let it go over your head.
别太自信了
Stop it !!
停
No Lucy!
不 露西!
Very good   fast.
很好 很快
Just like your father.
就像你的父亲一样
He never told you?
他从没跟你说过吗?
Burn.
烧吧
At this time of need,strengthen me.
在需要的时候,给我力量
You are my refuge and strength
你是我的避难所 我的力量
I do not fear for you or with me.
我并不怕 因你和我在一起
I won't let you go !!
我不会放手
You faith has failed you!
你的信仰不能保护你
No!
不
For the life of the flesh is in the blood.
肉体的生命是在血液中
And I have given you upon the altar
我现在放你到祭坛上
for the giving of your soul.
为了献出你的灵魂
How dare you come to this holy place?
你怎敢到这神圣的地方?
The man who defied the Church  for his own selfish crusade ?!
这家伙反抗教会 只为他自私的行动?
Inside the burning train just behind the city walls
在燃烧的火车上不过就是在城市的墙后
you'll find hundreds more like it.
你会找到数佰个像他一样
- And their queen was not among them.  - LIES !!
- 他们的女王不在其中  - 你说谎
This man is a charlatan.A risk to the security of cities.
这人是危险份子 会危害到城市的安全
There is no vampire manace!
没有吸血鬼
- The war is over   priest!  - No.
- 战争结束了 教士!  - 不
It's just beginning.
这才刚开始
I'll notify the others. We'll meet you at the rally point at City 7.
我去提醒其他人 我们在7号城市会合
God speed.
上帝祝福着(注:常用于 在人们踏上生命的征程时)